interment.net 2000-12-03

# Privacy Statement - Cemetery Records Online

| **Cemetery Directory**  
---  
**·** | 

United States  
  
**·** | Canada  
**·** | Australia   
**·** | New Zealand   
**·** | Ireland  
**·** | United Kingdom   
**·** | Other Countries   
  
**Other Features**  
---  
  
**·**

| The Cemetery Column  
**·** | Obituary Links  
**·** | Publish Your Works  
**·** | Find a Lost Burial  
**·** | Cemetery Bookstore  
**·** | Genealogy Shop  

  | 

###  Privacy Statement for Cemetery Records Online 

**Cemetery Records Online** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Cemetery Records Online ](http://www.interment.net/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information. This information is not disseminated, transferred or sold to anyone or any organization. The information is kept strictly confidential. The information is used to study site usage. 

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. __

####  Advertisers 

We use a variety of advertising networks to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site uses a form to submit burial records. The form asks for the users name, e-mail, and web site URL. This is information is used to credit the user for submitting the records. This information is optional. Users may withhold this information, and still participate.

Our site maintains a mailing list. Users must provide their e-mail address. Users will also be asked to provide some demographic information (state and country of residence, and age). The demographic information is not required. We use this information to identify the age groups of the visitors and from what areas of the world we get the most use. This information is kep strictly confidential.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Personal information is never shared or sold to anyone.

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Cemetery Records Online** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Special Relationships 

This site maintains special relationships with other organizations.

This site acts as reseller of goods and products from certain vendors and manufacturers. When clicking a link to purchase an item from this website, you will be asked to provide some information needed to complete the sale. This site does not use or retain that information; it is retained and used by the vendor or manufacturer. These vendors and manufacturers are:

>   * Allcensus
>   * Everton Genealogical Publishing
>   * Ancestry.com
>   * Harris Digital Publishing Group
>   * Amazon.com
>   * Irishop.com
>   * Ireland-Information.com
> 

This site is involved in a strategic partnership with Software Wonders of NJ [[http://www.daddezio.com](http://www.daddezio.com/)]. The partnership involves referring certain e-mail correspondence to each other. Only e-mail correspondence that appears to be best suited for the other site is referred.

#### Children's Guidelines 

This site meets **** the Online Privacy Protection Act guidelines. 

####  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us . 

  1. You can send email to [ steven@deltanet.com ](mailto:steven@deltanet.com)

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [ steven@deltanet.com ](mailto:steven@deltanet.com)

###  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
